<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" 
      xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
      xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" 
      xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" 
      version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Lisa Anders - questionable.quarto</title>
<link>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/site_map.html</link>
<atom:link href="https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/site_map.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<description>Making the most out of data</description>
<generator>quarto-1.4.550</generator>
<lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 06:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<item>
  <title>Black eyed peas bean cake</title>
  <dc:creator>Lisa Anders</dc:creator>
  <link>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/Black eyed peas bean cake.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 
<p>Loosely based on: <a href="https://southernbite.com/black-eyed-pea-cakes/" class="uri">https://southernbite.com/black-eyed-pea-cakes/</a></p>
<p>Black eyed peas can be canned or cooked using the Perini Ranch recipe: <a href="https://www.farmhousevineyard.com/recipe/perini-ranch-black-eyes-peas/" class="uri">https://www.farmhousevineyard.com/recipe/perini-ranch-black-eyes-peas/</a></p>
<section id="ingredients" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="ingredients">Ingredients</h2>
<p>Black eyed peas:</p>
<ul>
<li>1 lb Dried Farmhouse Vineyards Black Eyed Peas</li>
<li>1/4 cup Bacon Grease</li>
<li>1 tbsp Salt</li>
</ul>
<p>Bean griddle cake:</p>
<ul>
<li>4c black eyed beans (already cooked, I used the pereni farmhouse recipe)</li>
<li>~8tbs flour</li>
<li>~8tbs corn meal</li>
<li>~4 TBS bread crumbs</li>
<li>1-4 tsp smoked paprika</li>
<li>1-4 tsp cumin</li>
<li>1 egg</li>
<li>1 small onion + 1 glove garlic sauteed to clearness</li>
</ul>
<p>Sauce:</p>
<ul>
<li>1/2 cup mayo</li>
<li>Salt</li>
<li>Pepper</li>
<li>1/2 tsp Cajun seasoning</li>
<li>1 garlic clove, SMASHED</li>
</ul>
</section>
<section id="instructions" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="instructions">Instructions</h2>
<p>Make the beans:</p>
<ol type="1">
<li>Pre-soak dried peas for a minimum of 2 hours before cooking.</li>
<li>Adding water when needed.</li>
<li>Add bacon grease and salt.</li>
<li>Heat on medium high heat and stir occasionally.</li>
<li>Scoop out the foam that’s at the top of the pot.</li>
<li>Heat to 165 degrees and until peas are tender.</li>
</ol>
<p>Make the cakes and dipping sauce:</p>
<ul>
<li>Mix ingredients</li>
<li>Spoon roughly 3 tbsp of batter into hot pan</li>
<li>2 min front side, flip and 1.5-2 min back side</li>
</ul>


</section>
 ]]></description>
  <category>light-meal</category>
  <category>hearty-meal</category>
  <category>side-dish</category>
  <category>Jesse</category>
  <guid>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/Black eyed peas bean cake.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/img/bean cake.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Rosemary Chicken with Leeks and Beans</title>
  <dc:creator>Leite&#39;s Culinaria</dc:creator>
  <link>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/Rosemary Chicken with Leeks and Beans.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 
<section id="ingredients" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="ingredients">Ingredients</h2>
<p>2 tablespoons olive oil 2 pounds bone-in, skin-on chicken thighs, or legs Salt and freshly ground black pepper 1 pound leeks, white and light green only, cut into 1/4-inch coins, rinsed well 4 cloves garlic, chopped 2 tablespoons minced fresh rosemary, plus more leaves for garnish 1 cup apple cider, (not apple juice) or chicken stock if you prefer a more savory take One (15-ounce) can cannellini beans, drained and liquid reserved 3 tablespoons sour cream Zest of 1 lemon</p>
</section>
<section id="instructions" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="instructions">Instructions</h2>
<p>Crank up the oven to 350°F (175°C).</p>
<p>Heat the oil in a large pan or Dutch oven over medium-high heat.</p>
<p>Generously season the chicken pieces with salt and pepper. Place them skin-side down in the pan and sear until the skin is irresistibly golden brown, 12 to 15 minutes. Flip and cook a few minutes more. Transfer to a plate.</p>
<p>Lower the heat to medium, add the leeks, and cook, stirring occasionally, until they begin to soften, about 5 minutes.</p>
<p>Stir in the garlic and rosemary, season well with salt and pepper, and cook a minute more.</p>
<p>Nestle the chicken into the gorgeous greenery in the pan.</p>
<p>Splash in the apple cider.</p>
<p>Spoon the beans around the chicken and stir into the leeks. Add some of the reserved bean liquid if the leeks aren’t halfway covered with the cider.</p>
<p>Slide the pan into the oven and roast, uncovered, until the thighs are beautifully browned and register 165°F (74°C) on an instant-read thermometer and the beans are slightly crusted, 45 to 55 minutes. If the chicken is browning too quickly, cover the pan.</p>
<p>Remove the chicken from the oven and swirl in the sour cream.</p>
<p>Zest the lemon over the dish and carry it triumphantly to the table.</p>
</section>
<section id="lisas-notes" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="lisas-notes">Lisa’s notes</h2>
<p>Skip the sour cream! Not needed at all.</p>


</section>
 ]]></description>
  <category>light-meal</category>
  <category>hearty-meal</category>
  <category>Jesse</category>
  <guid>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/Rosemary Chicken with Leeks and Beans.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/img/leek-chicken-beans.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Cuban Beans and Rice</title>
  <dc:creator>Leite&#39;s Culinaria</dc:creator>
  <link>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/Cuban Beans and Rice.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 
<section id="ingredients" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="ingredients">Ingredients</h2>
<p>1 cup dried black beans 2 bay leaves 2 teaspoons kosher salt 3 slices bacon, coarsely chopped (about 100 g) 1 medium (7 oz) yellow onion, diced 1 medium (7 oz) green bell pepper, seeded and diced 3 cloves garlic, minced 1/2 teaspoon ground cumin 1/2 teaspoon dried oregano 1 cup long-grain white rice 1 3/4 cups store-bought or homemade chicken stock</p>
</section>
<section id="instructions" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="instructions">Instructions</h2>
<p>Place the beans in a large pot and cover with water by at least 3 inches (8 cm). Slide the pot in the refrigerator and let soak for at least 12 hours and up to 24 hours.</p>
<p>Drain the beans and return them to the pot. Add enough fresh cold water to cover the beans by about 1 inch (2.5 cm), toss in the bay leaves, and bring to a boil over high heat. Reduce the heat to medium-low and gently simmer until the beans are just tender, which can take anywhere from 45 to 90 minutes, depending on the age of your beans. Add the salt and continue to cook for 15 minutes more.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, in a large saucepan over medium-low heat, sauté the bacon until the fat has rendered and the bacon is crisp, 10 to 15 minutes. Using a slotted spoon, move the bacon to a stack of paper towels placed on a plate.</p>
<p>Add the onion and pepper to the pan and cook in the bacon fat until the vegetables soften, 8 to 10 minutes. Stir in the garlic, cumin, and oregano and cook, stirring, just until the garlic softens and the spice is fragrant, 2 to 4 minutes. Dump in the rice and stir constantly for a couple minutes to completely coat the rice with the bacon drippings. Then pour in the stock and bring to a boil. Lower the heat to a simmer, cover the pan, and cook until the liquid has been absorbed, 15 to 20 minutes.</p>
<p>When the beans are done, drain them, reserving at least 1/2 cup of the bean cooking liquid. Stir the beans into the pan containing the rice and continue cooking over medium-low heat until the rice is tender, 5 to 15 minutes more. If you need more liquid to fully cook the rice, use the reserved bean cooking liquid. Taste and adjust the seasoning to taste with salt. Stir in the bacon and serve the beans and rice immediately.</p>


</section>
 ]]></description>
  <category>hearty-meal</category>
  <category>potluck</category>
  <category>crock / instant pot</category>
  <category>Jesse</category>
  <guid>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/Cuban Beans and Rice.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/img/cuban-beans.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Instant Pot Pork Stew with Hominy</title>
  <dc:creator>Leite&#39;s Culinaria</dc:creator>
  <link>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/Instant Pot Pork Stew with Hominy.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 
<section id="at-a-glance" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="at-a-glance">At a Glance</h2>
<p>Nutrition:</p>
<p>Serving: 1 portion Calories: 208 kcal Carbohydrates: 25 g Protein: 14 g Fat: 6 g Saturated Fat: 2 g Monounsaturated Fat: 2 g Cholesterol: 37 mg Sodium: 1052 mg Fiber: 5 g Sugar: 4 g Nutrition information is automatically calculated, so should only be used as an approximation.</p>
</section>
<section id="ingredients" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="ingredients">Ingredients</h2>
<p>1 pound pork shoulder, cut into bite-size cubes 1 medium (8 oz) yellow onion, chopped One (25-ounce) can hominy, undrained 3/4 cup water 3 or 4 garlic cloves, chopped 1 to 3 canned chipotle chiles in adobo, chopped, with 1 to 2 teaspoons adobo sauce from the can (about 1/2 small can) 2 teaspoons ancho chile powder, plus more if needed 2 teaspoons ground cumin 1 teaspoon dried oregano 1 teaspoon kosher salt, plus more if needed 1/4 cup fresh cilantro, for garnish (omit or use parsley instead)</p>
</section>
<section id="instructions" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="instructions">Instructions</h2>
<p>In the insert of an Instant Pot or pressure cooker, combine the pork, onion, hominy and its juices, water, garlic, chipotle chiles, adobo sauce, ancho chile powder, cumin, oregano, and salt.</p>
<p>TESTER TIP: If you like your hominy more al dente, add half the can while cooking so it flavors and thickens the stew a bit, and save the other half to add after cooking.</p>
<p>Secure the lid on the Instant Pot or pressure cooker. Close the pressure-release valve. Cook over high pressure for 30 minutes. At the end of the cooking time, allow the pressure to release naturally, 15 to 20 minutes. The pork should be very tender.</p>
<p>Taste the stew and season with additional ancho chile powder and salt, if needed. Garnish with the cilantro and serve.</p>


</section>
 ]]></description>
  <category>hearty-meal</category>
  <category>potluck</category>
  <category>crock / instant pot</category>
  <category>Jesse</category>
  <guid>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/Instant Pot Pork Stew with Hominy.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/img/pozole_hominy.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Senate Bean Soup</title>
  <dc:creator>Leite&#39;s Culinaria</dc:creator>
  <link>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/senate beans.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 
<p>Adapted From Heirloom Beans, by Rancho Gordo!</p>
<section id="ingredients" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="ingredients">Ingredients</h2>
<p>1/2 pound dried navy beans* (or pretty much any variety of white bean) One (1 1/2-pound) smoked ham hock, cut crosswise into 3 or 4 pieces (you can ask your butcher to cut the ham hock for you) 6 cups water 1 bay leaf 1/2 medium yellow onion, chopped 4 celery stalks with leaves, chopped 2 garlic cloves, finely chopped 1/4 cup chopped flat-leaf parsley leaves, plus more for garnishing Salt and freshly ground pepper</p>
</section>
<section id="instructions" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="instructions">Instructions</h2>
<p>Rinse the beans in lots of cool water and gently run your hands over the beans, checking them for small bits of debris. Pour the beans into a pot and cover with about 1 inch of cold water. Let the beans soak for anywhere from 2 to 6 hours. Drain the beans.</p>
<p>In a soup pot, combine the beans, ham hock, water, and bay leaf. Bring to a boil, reduce the heat to low, and simmer gently until the beans are beginning to soften, about 1 hour.</p>
<p>Add the onion, celery, garlic, 1/4 cup parsley, salt, and pepper to taste. Continue to simmer until the beans are soft and beginning to break down, and the ham meat comes off the bone easily when shredded with a fork, about 1 hour.</p>
<p>Remove the ham hock pieces. When they are cool enough to handle, remove the meat from the bones. Dice the meat and return it to the pot. Taste and adjust the seasonings. Ladle the soup into warmed bowls and garnish with parsley.</p>
<p><strong>Instant Pot Senate Bean Soup Variation</strong></p>
<p>To make this Senate bean soup in your Instant Pot, do not soak the beans. Decrease the water to 5 cups and cook on the manual setting for 45 minutes. Let the Instant Pot release naturally.</p>
</section>
<section id="lisas-notes" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="lisas-notes">Lisa’s notes</h2>
<p>Super yummy!</p>


</section>
 ]]></description>
  <category>hearty-meal</category>
  <category>crock / instant pot</category>
  <category>Jesse</category>
  <guid>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/senate beans.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/img/senate_beans.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Baked Mochi Donuts</title>
  <dc:creator>Teak and thyme</dc:creator>
  <link>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/Mochi Donuts.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 
<section id="ingredients" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="ingredients">Ingredients</h2>
<p>MOCHI DONUTS</p>
<ul>
<li>150 g glutinous rice flour or mochiko</li>
<li>1 teaspoon baking powder</li>
<li>1/4 teaspoon salt</li>
<li>50 g unsalted butter, melted</li>
<li>50 g brown sugar</li>
<li>1 large egg, room temperature</li>
<li>200 g dairy or non-dairy milk</li>
<li>1 teaspoon vanilla extract</li>
</ul>
<p>MATCHA WHITE CHOCOLATE GLAZE</p>
<ul>
<li>100 g white chocolate, roughly chopped</li>
<li>1 teaspoon oil</li>
<li>1 teaspoon matcha powder, ceremonial grade recommended</li>
</ul>
<p>WHITE CHOCOLATE BISCOFF GLAZE</p>
<ul>
<li>100 g white chocolate, roughly chopped</li>
<li>1 teaspoon oil</li>
<li>1 Lotus biscuit, crushed</li>
</ul>
</section>
<section id="instructions" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="instructions">Instructions</h2>
<p>MOCHI DONUTS</p>
<p>Preheat oven to 350°F and lightly grease a donut pan with cooking spray or softened butter. Set aside. In a small bowl, stir together glutinous rice flour, baking powder, and salt. Set aside. In another small mixing bowl, stir together melted butter and brown sugar. Add in the egg and stir until the yolk has broken up and combined. Stir in the milk and vanilla extract. Add the dry mixture into the wet mixture and stir to combine until smooth. Spoon the batter (or use a piping bag) into the donut pan until almost full. Bake for 25-30 minutes until slightly browned on the edges. Stop at 25 minutes for softer donuts or 30 minutes for crisper donuts but be careful not to overbake otherwise they will be more hard than chewy. Let donuts cool in the pan for 5-10 minutes before lifting them out. Let cool completely on a wire rack before glazing.</p>
<p>MATCHA WHITE CHOCOLATE GLAZE</p>
<p>In a small pot, bring about 1” of water to a boil. In a heat-safe bowl that fits perfectly on top of the pot without touching the water, add the chopped white chocolate, oil, and matcha powder. Turn off the heat and place the bowl on top of pot to create a double boiler. Let the chocolate sit undisturbed for about 2-3 minutes until it has mostly melted. Stir with a spatula to mix the matcha and chocolate together and ensure there are no unmelted chunks. Transfer the melted chocolate to a small bowl. Dip the donuts into the chocolate and shake off the excess. Place on a wire rack to set. Drizzle with any remaining white chocolate if desired.</p>
<p>WHITE CHOCOLATE BISCOFF GLAZE</p>
<p>Use the same directions as the matcha glaze above but without the matcha powder. Sprinkle the glazed donuts with crushed biscuits while they’re still wet.</p>
<p>NOTES</p>
<p>Melting white chocolate in microwave: Microwave in 10 second intervals, stirring in between each zap. Stop when it’s mostly melted. Be careful not to overheat it otherwise the chocolate will seize. If you’re making both glazes, save time by melting all of the white chocolate (200g) together and divide into two bowls. Stir matcha powder into one half.</p>
</section>
<section id="lisas-notes" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="lisas-notes">Lisa’s notes</h2>
<p>I used Matcha Green Tea icing instead, and it was delicious! Mix together 1 tsp of matcha powder, 1 tbls milk / oat milk, and powdered sugar until it reaches a thick consistency.</p>


</section>
 ]]></description>
  <category>dessert</category>
  <category>vegetarian</category>
  <category>vegan</category>
  <category>Jesse</category>
  <guid>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/Mochi Donuts.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/img/donuts.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Chorizo Cabbage</title>
  <dc:creator>Jesse Frey</dc:creator>
  <link>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/Chorizo Cabbage.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 
<section id="ingredients" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="ingredients">Ingredients</h2>
<ul>
<li>Chorizo</li>
<li>Cabbage</li>
<li>Noodles</li>
</ul>
</section>
<section id="instructions" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="instructions">Instructions</h2>
<p>Cook noodles</p>
<p>While noodles cook stir fry together the cabbage and chorizo sausage.</p>
<p>Combine and eat!</p>
</section>
<section id="lisas-notes" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="lisas-notes">Lisa’s notes</h2>
<p>Delicious and easy!</p>


</section>
 ]]></description>
  <category>light-meal</category>
  <category>hearty-meal</category>
  <category>Jesse</category>
  <guid>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/Chorizo Cabbage.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/img/chorizo cabbage.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Chicken Shawarma</title>
  <dc:creator>Nagi </dc:creator>
  <link>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/Chicken Shawarma.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 
<section id="at-a-glance" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="at-a-glance">At a Glance</h2>
</section>
<section id="ingredients" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="ingredients">Ingredients</h2>
<p>1 kg / 2 lb chicken thigh fillets , skinless and boneless (Note 3)</p>
<p>Marinade</p>
<p>1 large garlic clove , minced (or 2 small cloves) 1 tbsp ground coriander 1 tbsp ground cumin 1 tbsp ground cardamon 1 tsp ground cayenne pepper (reduce to 1/2 tsp to make it not spicy) 2 tsp smoked paprika 2 tsp salt Black pepper 2 tbsp lemon juice 3 tbsp olive oil</p>
</section>
<section id="instructions" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="instructions">Instructions</h2>
<p>Marinade chicken - Combine the marinade ingredients in a large ziplock bag. Add the chicken, seal, the massage from the outside with your hands to make sure each piece is coated. Marinate 24 hours (minimum 3 hours). Yogurt Sauce - Combine the Yogurt Sauce ingredients in a bowl and mix. Cover and put in the fridge until required (it will last for 3 days in the fridge). Preheat stove or BBQ - Heat a large non-stick skillet with 1 tablespoon over medium high heat, or lightly brush a BBQ hotplate/grills with oil and heat to medium high. (See notes for baking) Cook chicken - Place chicken in the skillet or on the grill and cook the first side for 4 to 5 minutes until nicely charred. Turn and cook the other side for 3 to 4 minutes (the 2nd side takes less time). Rest - Remove chicken from the grill and cover loosely with foil. Set aside to rest for 5 minutes.</p>
<p>To Serve</p>
<p>Slice chicken and pile onto platter alongside flatbreads, Salad and the Yoghurt Sauce (or dairy free Tahini sauce from this recipe). To make a wrap, get a piece of flatbread and smear with Yoghurt Sauce. Top with a bit of lettuce and tomato and Chicken Shawarma. Roll up and enjoy!</p>
</section>
<section id="lisas-notes" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="lisas-notes">Lisa’s notes</h2>
<p>Serve with:</p>
<ul>
<li>Salad with garlic stuffed olives (dressing was 2 tbs lemon juice, 1 tbs olive oil, 1 tsp cumin)</li>
<li>Almond slivers and yellow jumbo raisins gently fried in butter</li>
<li>Rice perfumed with rose water</li>
</ul>


</section>
 ]]></description>
  <category>light-meal</category>
  <category>hearty-meal</category>
  <category>side-dish</category>
  <category>Jesse</category>
  <guid>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/Chicken Shawarma.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/img/chicken shawarma.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Chicken Biryani</title>
  <dc:creator>Random cookbook</dc:creator>
  <link>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/Chicken Biryani.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 
<div class="quarto-figure quarto-figure-center">
<figure class="figure">
<p><a href="img/biryani-chicken-recipe2.jpg" class="lightbox" data-glightbox="description: .lightbox-desc-1" data-gallery="quarto-lightbox-gallery-1" title="Biryani Chicken recipe"><img src="https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/img/biryani-chicken-recipe2.jpg" class="img-fluid figure-img" alt="Biryani Chicken recipe"></a></p>
<figcaption>Biryani Chicken recipe</figcaption>
</figure>
</div>



 ]]></description>
  <category>light-meal</category>
  <category>hearty-meal</category>
  <category>Jesse</category>
  <guid>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/Chicken Biryani.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/img/biryani-chicken.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Avocado pesto vegan sauce</title>
  <dc:creator>Plant based on a budget</dc:creator>
  <link>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/avocado pesto vegan sauce.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 
<section id="ingredients" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="ingredients">Ingredients</h2>
<p>1 cup of pistachios (walnuts will work too, or cashews) 2 large very ripe avocados 2 ounces of fresh basil leaves 4 garlic cloves 1 teaspoon of cumin ⅛ cup of olive oil (and more olive oil or water to get the desired consistency) ¼ fresh lemon Salt and pepper to taste Pasta of your choice</p>
</section>
<section id="instructions" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="instructions">Instructions</h2>
<p>In a medium pot over medium-high heat, cook the pasta according to the directions on the package.</p>
<p>While the pasta cooks, add the pistachios to the bowl of a food processor or high-powered blender and pulse until the nuts are broken down.</p>
<p>Add the avocados, basil, garlic, cumin to the bowl of the processor and wiz it on high. While the pesto is forming, slowly add the oil to the mix. Stop and scrape down the sides and taste. Add any salt or pepper at this time.</p>
<p>Drain your pasta, reserving 1 cup of the pasta water. Add the pasta and pesto in a large mixing bowl and toss around. Use the pasta water to thin out the pesto and a drizzle of fresh lemon juice, a little more salt and pepper to top it off.</p>
</section>
<section id="lisas-notes" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="lisas-notes">Lisa’s notes</h2>
<p>Added 2/3 teaspoon nutritional yeast (recommended from vegan recipes to give it more “parmesan” type flavor)</p>
<p>Substituted cashews instead of walnuts</p>


</section>
 ]]></description>
  <category>light-meal</category>
  <category>side-dish</category>
  <category>good-cold</category>
  <category>vegetarian</category>
  <category>vegan</category>
  <category>keto</category>
  <category>potluck</category>
  <category>Jesse</category>
  <guid>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/avocado pesto vegan sauce.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/img/avocado pesto.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Chicken Tortilla Soup Recipe</title>
  <dc:creator>Natasha&#39;s Kitchen</dc:creator>
  <link>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/Tortilla soup.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 
<section id="ingredients" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="ingredients">Ingredients</h2>
<p><strong>Chicken Tortilla Soup</strong></p>
<p>1 Tbsp olive oil 1 medium onion, chopped 3 garlic cloves, minced 1 jalapeno pepper , seeded and diced 1 tsp ground cumin 1 tsp chilli powder 1 lb chicken breasts, (2 medium) 20 oz can crushed tomatoes 32 oz chicken broth 14 oz can black beans, drained and rinsed 14 oz can corn, drained and rinsed 1/2 cup cilantro, chopped, divided (reserve 1/4 of it for garnish) 1 lime, juiced 1 tsp salt, or to taste</p>
<p><strong>Homemade Tortilla Strips</strong></p>
<p>1/4 cup olive oil 8 corn tortillas , (6” tortillas)</p>
<p><strong>Toppings</strong></p>
<p>1 large avocado, diced 1 lime, cut into wedges, to serve Radishes, diced thin</p>
</section>
<section id="instructions" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="instructions">Instructions</h2>
<p>Tortilla Strips:</p>
<p>Preheat a pan with 1/4 cup oil over medium-high heat. Cut tortillas into thin strips and fry them in batches in the hot oil until crisp. Remove from the pan and allow them to drain on a paper towel. Repeat with remaining tortilla strips, adding more oil as needed then set aside.</p>
<p>Chicken Tortilla Soup:</p>
<p>Preheat a pot with oil over medium-high heat. Add chopped onion, garlic and chopped jalapeño and sauté until veggies soften.</p>
<p>Add whole chicken breasts, corn, beans, chilli powder, cumin, crushed tomatoes, salt, ¼ cup of cilantro and chicken broth. Bring to a boil and let simmer for at least 25 minutes.</p>
<p>Remove chicken from the pot and shred it using 2 forks. Add shredded chicken back to the soup and simmer another 5 minutes then add lime juice.</p>
<p>Serve the soup with some tortilla strips, pieces of avocado, fresh cilantro and lime wedges.</p>
</section>
<section id="lisas-notes" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="lisas-notes">Lisa’s notes</h2>


</section>
 ]]></description>
  <category>hearty-meal</category>
  <category>Jesse</category>
  <guid>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/Tortilla soup.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/img/tortilla soup.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Gumbo</title>
  <dc:creator>Leite&#39;s Culinaria</dc:creator>
  <link>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/gumbo.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 
<section id="at-a-glance" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="at-a-glance">At a Glance</h2>
<p>Serving: 1portion | Calories: 855kcal | Carbohydrates: 48g | Protein: 43g | Fat: 55g | Saturated Fat: 13g | Polyunsaturated Fat: 20g | Monounsaturated Fat: 18g | Trans Fat: 1g | Cholesterol: 150mg | Sodium: 945mg | Potassium: 920mg | Fiber: 3g | Sugar: 3g</p>
</section>
<section id="ingredients" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="ingredients">Ingredients</h2>
<ul>
<li>3/4 cup mild vegetable oil</li>
<li>3/4 cup all-purpose flour</li>
<li>3 medium (about 12 oz) red, orange, and/or yellow bell peppers, seeded and thinly sliced</li>
<li>2 medium (about 3 1/2 oz) celery stalks, diced</li>
<li>4 garlic cloves, minced</li>
<li>1 medium (about 8 oz) yellow onion, diced</li>
<li>One (14-ounce) can fire-roasted diced tomatoes</li>
<li>1 tablespoon dried oregano</li>
<li>1 tablespoon dried thyme</li>
<li>1 tablespoon dried basil</li>
<li>1 tablespoon Creole seasoning</li>
<li>1 teaspoon chili powder</li>
<li>1 teaspoon ground cayenne pepper, or more or less to taste</li>
<li>Kosher salt and freshly ground black pepper</li>
<li>6 cups canned chicken broth or homemade chicken stock</li>
<li>1 pound andouille sausage (3 links), halved and sliced - - 1/2-inch (12-mm) thick</li>
<li>2 pounds skinless, bone-in chicken thighs</li>
<li>3 cups cooked rice, for serving</li>
<li>Fresh parsley, for serving</li>
</ul>
</section>
<section id="instructions" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="instructions">Instructions</h2>
<ul>
<li>In a large pot over medium heat, whisk together the oil and flour, and cook until the mixture turns golden brown, 8 to 10 minutes.</li>
<li>Stir in the bell peppers, celery, garlic, onion, tomatoes, oregano, thyme, basil, Creole seasoning, chili powder, cayenne, and a large pinch each of salt and pepper. The roux will bubble and thicken up immediately into a paste that coats the vegetables.</li>
<li>Continue to cook over medium heat, stirring occasionally, until the vegetables begin to soften, about 8 minutes.</li>
<li>Stir in the broth, sausage, and chicken. Bring the gumbo to a boil, reduce the heat, cover, and gently simmer until the chicken is literally falling apart, at least 3 hours or up to all day (the longer the better as the flavors will meld).</li>
<li>Skim the fat off the surface of the gumbo. Remove and discard the chicken bones.</li>
<li>Divvy the rice among bowls and ladle the gumbo over the rice. Garnish with parsley. Store any leftovers refrigerated in an airtight container for up to 3 days.</li>
</ul>
<p>HOW TO MAKE THIS IN YOUR SLOW COOKER, PRESSURE COOKER, OR INSTANT POT</p>
<p>Pressure Cooker Or Instant Pot Variation</p>
<p>To make this chicken gumbo in the pressure cooker or Instant Pot use the sauté function to cook the roux as described in step 1 of the recipe above. Stir in the remaining ingredients, except the rice and parsley, lock the lid in place, and cook over high pressure for 35 minutes. Release the pressure, remove the lid, and discard the bones. Use the sauté function to bring the gumbo to a boil and simmer until slightly thickened, about 5 minutes. Serve over rice, garnished with parsley. Slow Cooker Variation</p>
<p>To make this chicken gumbo in the slow cooker, follow step 1 in the recipe above, then add the roux, and all remaining ingredients except the rice and parsley, to the slow cooker. Cover and cook until the chicken is falling off the bones, 6 to 8 hours on low, or 5 to 6 hours on high. Uncover, discard the chicken bones, then cook on high until the gumbo thickens slightly, 20 to 30 minutes. Serve over rice, garnished with parsley.</p>
</section>
<section id="lisas-notes" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="lisas-notes">Lisa’s notes</h2>
<p>How can you go wrong with gumbo?</p>
<p>Use gluten free flour (with added xantham gum) for a gluten free experience.</p>
<p>Add some okra to bring it up a notch further.</p>


</section>
 ]]></description>
  <category>hearty-meal</category>
  <category>crock / instant pot</category>
  <category>Jesse</category>
  <guid>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/gumbo.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/img/gumbo.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Flourless Chocolate Cayenne Cake</title>
  <dc:creator>David Leite</dc:creator>
  <link>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/flourless chocolate cayenne cake.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 
<section id="at-a-glance" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="at-a-glance">At a Glance</h2>
<p>Serving: 1portion | Calories: 381kcal | Carbohydrates: 29g | Protein: 5g | Fat: 28g | Saturated Fat: 17g | Polyunsaturated Fat: 1g | Monounsaturated Fat: 8g | Trans Fat: 1g | Cholesterol: 112mg | Sodium: 180mg | Potassium: 235mg | Fiber: 3g | Sugar: 23g | Vitamin A: 644IU | Vitamin C: 0.1mg | Calcium: 35mg | Iron: 3mg</p>
</section>
<section id="ingredients" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="ingredients">Ingredients</h2>
<p>11 tablespoons unsalted butter, plus more for the pan 7 ounces 70% dark chocolate, chopped 1/2 teaspoon cayenne pepper, or more, to taste 1/3 cup espresso or strong coffee, cooled 1/2 teaspoon vanilla extract 3 large eggs 2/3 cup superfine sugar, (or just blitz granulated sugar in a blender until finely ground but not powdery 1/2 teaspoon sea salt 2 tablespoons cocoa powder, for dusting</p>
</section>
<section id="instructions" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="instructions">Instructions</h2>
<p>Preheat the oven to 350°F (180°C). Butter a 8-inch (20-cm) springform pan and line the bottom with parchment paper.</p>
<p>In a small saucepan over low heat, warm the butter, chocolate, and cayenne pepper until the chocolate melts, 5 to 10 minutes. Remove from the heat and stir in the coffee and vanilla. Remove from the heat and let cool.</p>
<p>Using a stand mixer or handheld mixer on medium-high speed, whisk together the eggs and sugar until thick, pale, and fluffy, 3 to 5 minutes.</p>
<p>Pour the cooled chocolate mixture into the eggs, add the salt, and use a spatula to gently fold until everything is combined. Scrape the batter into the prepared pan and bake until the cake is just cooked through with a slight wobble in the middle, 38 to 45 minutes.</p>
<p>Remove from the oven and let the cake cool completely. As it cools, the surface will crack, and this is what you want!</p>
<p>If desired, dump some cocoa powder in a small strainer and tap it over the cake to generously dust it before serving.</p>
</section>
<section id="lisas-notes" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="lisas-notes">Lisa’s notes</h2>
<p>We used 3/4 tsp cayenne and it was perfect.</p>
<p>Yes it’s whole eggs. I triple checked that it wasn’t a meringue, but somehow it works out!</p>


</section>
 ]]></description>
  <category>dessert</category>
  <category>Jesse</category>
  <guid>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/flourless chocolate cayenne cake.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/img/flourless chocolate cayenne cake.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Cranberry Sauce</title>
  <dc:creator>Mom on timeout</dc:creator>
  <link>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/Cranberry Sauce.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 
<section id="ingredients" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="ingredients">Ingredients</h2>
<p>¾ cup sugar ½ cup orange juice ½ cup water 12 oz fresh cranberries rinsed and picked through pinch of salt 1 cinnamon stick 1 piece of orange peel just use a potato peel or paring knife</p>
</section>
<section id="instructions" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="instructions">Instructions</h2>
<p>Combine sugar, orange juice, and water in a large saucepan over medium heat. Stir to combine. Add cranberries, salt, cinnamon stick and orange peel. Bring to a simmer over medium heat, stirring frequently. Continue cooking, for about 10 minutes, or until all or most of the cranberries have popped. I like to leave a handful of berries whole. Let cool for at least 30 minutes. Cover and refrigerate until ready to use. Can be made up to 3 days in advance.</p>
</section>
<section id="lisas-notes" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="lisas-notes">Lisa’s notes</h2>


</section>
 ]]></description>
  <category>side-dish</category>
  <category>good-cold</category>
  <category>vegetarian</category>
  <category>vegan</category>
  <category>Jesse</category>
  <guid>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/Cranberry Sauce.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/img/cranberry-sauce.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Tamale Pie</title>
  <dc:creator>America&#39;s Test Kitchen</dc:creator>
  <link>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/tamale-pie.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 
<div class="quarto-figure quarto-figure-center">
<figure class="figure">
<p><a href="img/tamale pie 2.jpg" class="lightbox" data-glightbox="description: .lightbox-desc-1" data-gallery="quarto-lightbox-gallery-1" title="Tamale pie recipe"><img src="https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/img/tamale pie 2.jpg" class="img-fluid figure-img" alt="Tamale pie recipe"></a></p>
<figcaption>Tamale pie recipe</figcaption>
</figure>
</div>
<section id="lisas-notes" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="lisas-notes">Lisa’s notes</h2>
<p>Using a spoon to smooth out the cornbread topping is a lie, consider rolling it out or piping it instead.</p>



</section>
 ]]></description>
  <category>hearty-meal</category>
  <category>Jesse</category>
  <guid>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/tamale-pie.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/img/tamale pie.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Soba Noodles with Roasted Eggplant and Sesame</title>
  <dc:creator>America&#39;s Test Kitchen</dc:creator>
  <link>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/seseme noodle.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 
<div class="quarto-figure quarto-figure-center">
<figure class="figure">
<p><a href="img/seseme noodles 2.jpg" class="lightbox" data-gallery="quarto-lightbox-gallery-1" data-glightbox="description: .lightbox-desc-1" title="Seseme noodles recipe"><img src="https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/img/seseme noodles 2.jpg" class="img-fluid figure-img" alt="Seseme noodles recipe"></a></p>
<figcaption>Seseme noodles recipe</figcaption>
</figure>
</div>
<section id="lisas-notes" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="lisas-notes">Lisa’s notes</h2>
<p>Super good cold on a hot day.</p>



</section>
 ]]></description>
  <category>hearty-meal</category>
  <category>good-cold</category>
  <category>vegetarian</category>
  <category>vegan</category>
  <category>Jesse</category>
  <guid>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/seseme noodle.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/img/eggplant soba noodle.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Saffron rice with meat almond and raison toppings</title>
  <dc:creator>Yasmeen Binno</dc:creator>
  <link>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/saffron rice with meat almond and raison toppings.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 
<div class="quarto-figure quarto-figure-center">
<figure class="figure">
<p><a href="img/saffron rice with meat almond and raison toppings.jpg" class="lightbox" data-glightbox="description: .lightbox-desc-1" data-gallery="quarto-lightbox-gallery-1" title="saffron rice with meat almond and raison toppings recipe"><img src="https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/img/saffron rice with meat almond and raison toppings.jpg" class="img-fluid figure-img" alt="saffron rice with meat almond and raison toppings recipe"></a></p>
<figcaption>saffron rice with meat almond and raison toppings recipe</figcaption>
</figure>
</div>
<section id="lisas-notes" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="lisas-notes">Lisa’s notes</h2>
<p>Using the full amount of butter is very very rich, consider using less if you want something healthier (still delicious). Salad on the side really balances it, yum.</p>



</section>
 ]]></description>
  <category>hearty-meal</category>
  <category>Jesse</category>
  <guid>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/saffron rice with meat almond and raison toppings.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/img/saffron rice with meat almond and raison toppings 2.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Pear and ginger crisp</title>
  <link>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/Pear and ginger crisp.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 
<div class="quarto-figure quarto-figure-center">
<figure class="figure">
<p><a href="img/pear and ginger crisp.jpg" class="lightbox" data-gallery="quarto-lightbox-gallery-1" data-glightbox="description: .lightbox-desc-1" title="Pear and ginger recipe"><img src="https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/img/pear and ginger crisp.jpg" class="img-fluid figure-img" alt="Pear and ginger recipe"></a></p>
<figcaption>Pear and ginger recipe</figcaption>
</figure>
</div>
<section id="lisas-notes" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="lisas-notes">Lisa’s notes</h2>
<p>Heavenly</p>



</section>
 ]]></description>
  <category>good-cold</category>
  <category>dessert</category>
  <category>Jesse</category>
  <guid>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/Pear and ginger crisp.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/img/pear and ginger crisp.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Pad Thai</title>
  <link>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/pad thai.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 
<section id="at-a-glance" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="at-a-glance">At a Glance</h2>
</section>
<section id="ingredients" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="ingredients">Ingredients</h2>
<p>Ingredients for Pad Thai Sauce (makes four large servings)</p>
<p>1/4 cup palm sugar 1/4 cup fish sauce 1 tablespoon tamarind concentrate 1/4 cup Sriracha sauce (We use Shark brand. Use less for a mild taste)</p>
<p>Ingredients for Pad Thai (makes 2 servings)</p>
<p>1 egg lightly beaten 3/4 cup (or more) fresh shrimp, uncooked 1 tablespoon sliced shallot 1 tablespoon chopped salted radish 1/4 cup diced firm tofu 1 handful rice stick noodle – replace with broccoli slaw 1/4 cup plus 2 tablespoons water 1 cup fresh bean sprouts 1/4 cup fresh chives, cut into one inch long pieces 1 tablespoon sugar 2 tablespoons chopped roasted peanut vegetable oil for frying</p>
</section>
<section id="instructions" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="instructions">Instructions</h2>
<p>Method for Pad Thai Sauce</p>
<ul>
<li>Put tamarind concentrate into a measuring cup, and add enough water to make 1/4 cup, stir, this is your tamarind juice.</li>
<li>In a small sauce pan, put palm sugar, fish sauce, tamarind juice, and sriracha sauce. Cook on low heat until the palm sugar dissolves, then increase heat. Let it start to boil, then qquickly remove from heat, and set aside. You can make this Pad Thai sauce ahead and put in a jar in the fridge up to a week.</li>
</ul>
<p>Method for Pad Thai</p>
<ul>
<li>Rinse the radish several times under cold water, gently squeezing off the water. Chop it and add a little bit of sugar to sweeten, mix well.</li>
<li>Soak the rice stick noodle in warm water for about 15 minutes, leave in water until you are ready to use.</li>
<li>Heat 1 tablespoon of oil in a wok at medium-high heat. Add egg and cook it quickly, scrambling into small pieces (see video below). Remove, set aside.</li>
<li>Add 2 tablespoons of oil in the same wok. Add shrimps and cook until done. Transfer to a bowl, set aside.</li>
<li>Add 1 tablespoon of oil to the wok. Add shallot, radish and tofu fry until aromatic. Increase the heat of your wok. Add a handful of soaked noodles followed with water. Stir-fry this mixture for about 5-6 minutes. The noodles will start to get soft. Add 1/4 cup of Pad Thai Sauce and mix well. Add sugar, cooked egg, bean sprout, chive and cooked shrimps. Stir well for another 1-2 minutes until everything blends together. Turn off heat, transfer to serving plate with sliced fresh lime, roasted peanuts, and more bean sprout on the side. Now dazzle your friends with the fact that your Pad Thai looks and tastes just as good as any restaurant. Enjoy!</li>
<li>You may add Thai chili powder, sugar and crushed peanuts at the table on the side.</li>
</ul>
</section>
<section id="lisas-notes" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="lisas-notes">Lisa’s notes</h2>


</section>
 ]]></description>
  <category>light-meal</category>
  <category>good-cold</category>
  <category>vegetarian</category>
  <category>Jesse</category>
  <guid>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/pad thai.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/img/pad thai.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Oatmeal chocolate chunk ice cream sandwhiches</title>
  <dc:creator>Samantha Seneviratne</dc:creator>
  <link>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/oatmeal chocolate chunk ice cream sandwhiches.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 
<div class="quarto-figure quarto-figure-center">
<figure class="figure">
<p><a href="img/oatmeal chocolate chunk ice cream sandwhiches.jpg" class="lightbox" data-gallery="quarto-lightbox-gallery-1" data-glightbox="description: .lightbox-desc-1" title="Oatmeal chocolate chunk ice cream sandwhiches recipe"><img src="https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/img/oatmeal chocolate chunk ice cream sandwhiches.jpg" class="img-fluid figure-img" alt="Oatmeal chocolate chunk ice cream sandwhiches recipe"></a></p>
<figcaption>Oatmeal chocolate chunk ice cream sandwhiches recipe</figcaption>
</figure>
</div>
<section id="lisas-notes" class="level2">
<h2 data-anchor-id="lisas-notes">Lisa’s notes</h2>
<p>This icecream sandwich is super good. The recommendation is cinnamon ice cream, but dark chocolate chunk ice cream was also super good.</p>



</section>
 ]]></description>
  <category>good-cold</category>
  <category>dessert</category>
  <category>vegetarian</category>
  <category>Jesse</category>
  <guid>https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/oatmeal chocolate chunk ice cream sandwhiches.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://questionable.quarto.pub/recipes/recipes/img/oatmeal chocolate chunk ice cream sandwhiches 2.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
